Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 1=
(City Lord's Mansion)
(Mu Yunqing, Lord of Jin City)
Yunqing.
(Yu Yingwan, Wife)
Hand over the City Lord's Token.
I'll spare your miserable life.
I'd rather die than give it to you.
If you refuse to cooperate with Mobei,
then surrender your life!
Let go of me!
Yunqing.
Wan, I can't protect you anymore.
If there's a next life,
let's be husband and wife again.
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪How long must I wait, till youth fades♪
♪And hair turns white♪
♪If fate allows♪
♪May our eyes meet♪
♪Across time♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
(Yunqing, in the next life,
I'll be the one to protect you.)
(What a strange dream I had.)
(City Lord's Mansion)
(What grudge exists
between Mobei and the City Lord?)
(I must uncover the truth and stop
this nightmare becoming reality.)
(These are the red arrows for dispelling
bad omens before entering.)
Yunqing, what are you doing?
I want to call it off.
Nonsense!
(Canceling it?)
(He doesn't want to marry me?)
She's not the one I want.
What did you say?
Don't think Grandfather's support
guarantees your entry.
I have no feelings for you.
(Mu Fengrong, Former City Lord
Mu Yunhao, Eldest Son)
Grandfather.
Please calm down.
We were betrothed in childhood.
It's not something you can accept
or reject at will.
I was carried here
in the grand sedan chair,
and this mansion
will be my home.
Even if you marry me,
I'll never consummate our marriage.
- Why shout?
- What happened?
(Why am I sleeping with him?)
(How could I...?)
My lord, my lady, what's wrong?
Do you want to wash up?
Okay.
(I shouldn't drink.)
(12 hours ago)
You tried to kill me
with the red arrows
to cancel our engagement?
Do you think
I can be discarded so easily?
You formally proposed with proper rites,
but now you resist endlessly.
Why?
Answer me.
Look at yourself.
Vulgar and rude,
a drunkard by nature.
Are you worthy to marry me?
Fine.
I'll grant your wish.
You don't kill me?
I'm not foolish enough to trade
my life for yours.
Since you refuse to sleep with me,
I'll find entertainment elsewhere.
Go ahead.
Go.
(The assassins came as in my dream.)
(Could this dream be a premonition?)
(City Lord's guard, Wei Feng)
Are you two okay?
Who sent you?
Keep this thing quiet.
Take them away.
Yes. Take them away.
You attracted assassins
immediately after arriving,
bringing chaos to our home.
You accuse me of bringing assassins?
Where's your proof?
Then explain this.
Why do you have this totem?
(2 hours ago)
My lady, you summoned me?
Investigate this totem.
(My lord ordered me to watch her.)
(She looks suspicious.)
(What is she doing?)
(Is she plotting something?)
(Liu Bingmo, Yu Yingwan's guard)
Yes, I'll.
My lord.
She ordered Liu Bingmo
to investigate a symbol.
I managed to copy it.
This is a Mobei assassin group's totem.
What's your connection to Mobei?
What are you scheming?
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪